

Manjunath Ganiga 8861316783 manjunath.katkeri@gmail.com

# **Summary**

A highly motivated Technology Enthusiast working as a Network Engineer and experienced on Network area of Routing, Switching, Palo Alto Firewall, Checkpoint Firewall, Cisco ASA firewall.

Exemplary problem-solving skills and enjoy doing planning, designing and analysis of new products and features to deliver optimum solutions by building relationships with colleagues, customer, stakeholders, and vendors.

# **Professional Experience:**

Having a total experience of **8 years** in various positions as shown below:

- I am currently working as a **Network Engineer** at **Algonomy Software Pvt. Ltd.**, Lavelle Road, Bangalore, from October 2020.
- Worked as Information Security Engineer at 22by7 Solution Pvt. Ltd, JP Nagar, Bangalore from April 2017 – September 2020.
- Worked as an Onsite Engineer for Jawaharlal Nehru Centre for Advanced Scientific Research (JNCASR), Jakkur, Bangalore from April 2017 to November 2017 (Outsourced from 22by7 Solutions Pvt. Ltd).
- Worked as an **Intern at 22by7 Solution Pvt. Ltd**, JP Nagar, Bangalore, from November 2016 to March 2017.

#### Skills:

- Networking: Routing, Switching, VLAN.
- Network Security: Firewall, Zscaler, VPN.
- Cloud Services (AWS): VPC, EC2, S3, IAM, Route 53.
- Server: AD, DHCP, DNS, FTP, ADFS SSO.
- Virtualization: VMware, Hyper-V.
- Operating Systems: Windows, Mac, Linux
- Tools: Putty, WinSCP.
- Ticketing Tools: Jira, ManageEngine ServiceDesk.
- Having hands on experience in Wireshark tool.

## **Algonomy Software Private Limited**

### Job Role:

My role involves maintaining the on-premises infrastructure network.

- Managing firewall (Checkpoint, Cisco ASA) configurations, monitoring the traffic, bandwidth utilization of applications, users, generating the reports, troubleshooting the network issues.
- Troubleshooting of Client VPN, Site to Site VPN.
- VPN establishment to AWS network.
- Troubleshooting the issues related to the production URLs.
- Have done some migrations Emails, Domain Controller, DHCP, VPN.
- Managing the Security Solutions SentinelOne (Endpoint), Perception Point (Email), McAfee (Endpoint DLP).

Currently handling 2 projects. Palo Alto Firewall Implementation and Aruba Wireless Implementation at Office Premise.

Palo Alto Firewall Implementation:

- Migration of Checkpoint and Cisco ASA firewall to Palo Alto firewall.
- Migrated all security policies, Remote access VPN configurations, NAT Policies.
- Troubleshooting the network related issues in Palo Alto.

Aruba Wireless Implementation:

Migration of Wireless from Cisco to Aruba Wireless. Handled the implementation of Aruba Wireless from start to end.

### 22by7 Solution Pvt Ltd

#### Job Role:

My role involves leveraging extensive IT expertise in the Information Security domain, with a focus on the implementation, upgradation, and support of firewalls, Zscaler, McAfee, and Symantec Antivirus, as well as Data Loss Prevention (DLP) solutions.

## **Projects:**

- McAfee ENS, DLP Deployment at Trianz.
- McAfee ENS Deployment at Visionet Systems, Bangalore.
- McAfee DLP Deployment at Manthan Systems.
- McAfee ENS, DLP Implementation at CSG.
- Zscaler Deployment in INFINITE COMPUTER SOLUTIONS BANGALORE.
- Symantec Data Loss Prevention Deployment in **INFINITE COMPUTER SOLUTIONS BANGALORE.**
- Symantec Data Loss Prevention Deployment in AEGIS GLOBAL.
- Symantec Endpoint Protection Implementation at SWIGGY.
- Symantec Endpoint Protection Implementation at CUREFIT.
- Checkpoint Firewall Implementation at ITC Infotech.
- Checkpoint Firewall Upgradation in MANTHAN SYSTEMS.
- Checkpoint Upgradation in ITC INFOTECH.

### **Certifications:**

- Cisco Certified Network Associate (CCNA Routing & Switching) certification.
- Zscaler ZCCA-IA Certification.
- McAfee Endpoint Solutions Certification.
- McAfee Data Solutions Certification.

### **Educational Qualification:**

- BE-ECE (VTU) from KSSEM, Bangalore with 64% aggregation-2016.
- PUC (Karnataka Pre-University Board) from Government PU College, Koteshwara with 71% aggregation-2012.
- SSLC (Karnataka Secondary Education Board) from Government School, Koteshwara with 72% aggregation-2010.

#### **Awards and Achievements:**

Awarded two times.

Icon Award- January 2019 & October 2019.

"For Outstanding Performance and Co-ordination Resulting in Quality Output"

- Got an appreciation mail from **FUNGIBLE** for successful migration of network infra from old office to new office.
- Got an appreciation mail from one of our customers for rebuilding the Symantec Endpoint Protection and Symantec Encryption Servers at the time of Ransomware attack.

### **Personal Details:**

Full Name: Manjunatha Ganiga Father's Name: Shripada Ganiga

Date of Birth: 14-08-1994 Mobile: +91 8861316783

Languages Known: Kannada, English, Hindi, Telugu.

#### **Declaration:**

I do hereby declare that the above statements mentioned in my resume are true and correct to the best of my knowledge and belief.

YOURS TRULY
MANJUNATH G